{
    "easy": [
        {
            "front": "6th string, open.",
            "back": "E"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 1st fret.",
            "back": "F"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 2nd fret.",
            "back": "F# / G♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 3rd fret.",
            "back": "G"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 4th fret.",
            "back": "G# / A♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 5th fret.",
            "back": "A"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 6th fret.",
            "back": "A# / B♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 7th fret.",
            "back": "B"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 8th fret.",
            "back": "C"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 9th fret.",
            "back": "C# / D♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 10th fret.",
            "back": "D"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 11th fret.",
            "back": "D# / E♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 12th fret.",
            "back": "E"
        }
    ],
    "medium": [
        {
            "front": "6th string, open.",
            "back": "E"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 1st fret.",
            "back": "F"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 2nd fret.",
            "back": "F# / G♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 3rd fret.",
            "back": "G"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 4th fret.",
            "back": "G# / A♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 5th fret.",
            "back": "A"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 6th fret.",
            "back": "A# / B♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 7th fret.",
            "back": "B"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 8th fret.",
            "back": "C"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 9th fret.",
            "back": "C# / D♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 10th fret.",
            "back": "D"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 11th fret.",
            "back": "D# / E♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "6th string, 12th fret.",
            "back": "E"
        },
        {
            "front": "5th string, open.",
            "back": "A"
        },
        {
            "front": "5th string, 1st fret.",
            "back": "A# / B♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "5th string, 2nd fret.",
            "back": "B"
        },
        {
            "front": "5th string, 3rd fret.",
            "back": "C"
        },
        {
            "front": "5th string, 4th fret.",
            "back": "C# / D♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "5th string, 5th fret.",
            "back": "D"
        },
        {
            "front": "5th string, 6th fret.",
            "back": "D# / E♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "5th string, 7th fret.",
            "back": "E"
        },
        {
            "front": "5th string, 8th fret.",
            "back": "F"
        },
        {
            "front": "5th string, 9th fret.",
            "back": "F# / G♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "5th string, 10th fret.",
            "back": "G"
        },
        {
            "front": "5th string, 11th fret.",
            "back": "G# / A♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "5th string, 12th fret.",
            "back": "A"
        },
        {
            "front": "4th string, open.",
            "back": "D"
        },
        {
            "front": "4th string, 1st fret.",
            "back": "D# / E♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "4th string, 2nd fret.",
            "back": "E"
        },
        {
            "front": "4th string, 3rd fret.",
            "back": "F"
        },
        {
            "front": "4th string, 4th fret.",
            "back": "F# / G♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "4th string, 5th fret.",
            "back": "G"
        },
        {
            "front": "4th string, 6th fret.",
            "back": "G# / A♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "4th string, 7th fret.",
            "back": "A"
        },
        {
            "front": "4th string, 8th fret.",
            "back": "A# / B♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "4th string, 9th fret.",
            "back": "B"
        },
        {
            "front": "4th string, 10th fret.",
            "back": "C"
        },
        {
            "front": "4th string, 11th fret.",
            "back": "C# / D♭"
        },
        {
            "front": "4th string, 12th fret.",
            "back": "D"
        }
    ],
    "hard": [
        {
            "front": "Sorry! Hard isn't ready yet!",
            "back": "Sorry! Hard isn't ready yet!"
        }
    ]
}